Noam Handelman

Full Stack Developer | Backend Developer

Languages

- Hebrew
- English
- Arabic

Education

Diploma (Bagrut), *Ironi Gimel High School* 2015 – 2018

Specializing on the following professions: Computer Science, Arabic, Maths and English

Skills

TypeScrypt/JavaScript

Java (Spring Boot) • Node.js • Docker

React.js • MongoDB • redis

PostgreSQL • AWS • Git • HTMLCSS

swagger

About Me

A developer with a great passion for the worlds of software and coding, for solving complex problems and creating an optimal user experience, who can spend hours in front of the screen in order to create a perfect product, with a hunger for never-ending learning, I will start a bachelor's degree in computer science this year and I am available for a full-time position.

Professional Experience

Application Engineer, Au10tix

01/2022 - 01/2023

- Providing solutions in the field of supervised machine learning and image analysis using the company's internal tools.
- Maintenance, optimizations and configurations of the company's products according to the customer's needs.

Intelligence & data Analyst, *Israeli Military Intelligence - Unit 8200* 09/2018 – 05/2021

Production and analysis of intelligence materials at a high level of classification using advanced technological systems in spoken and written Arabic.

Projects

Fitbuddy 🛮

Development and deployment of a full stack social media application using modern technologies to provide users with an engaging platform for creating and sharing content.

- Client side **TypeScript**, **React + Next.js** for UI, **NextAuth** for users authentication, **TailwindCss** for styling, **Zod** as a validator ☑
- Server side TypeScript, Express.js, MongoDB as a database,
 Mongoose as an ORM, AWS S3 + CloudFront for saving and serving users images, Zod as a validator, swagger for API documentation
- API documentation ☑

chatbot 🛮

Development and deployment of a chatbot that can provide a list of products from Amazon and jokes according to the user's request using **scraping** techniques and **webhooks.**

 Tech stack - Java, SpringBoot ,Docker for packaging the app and Dialogflow for the chatbot interface and swagger ☑

porfolio 🛮

 Tech stack - TypeScript, React + Vite for UI, TailwindCss and Framer Motion for styling and EmailJs ☑